The
battle
of the
because
Lula da da over
that of the
balloon
about
us
was
wooed
her without her that
her who would
lose it was
losing.
Battle
of
that
the end of the battle
of the about.
Was allowed the tube
that.
Louis was
wooed
Thank you Lou
The owner
would move the old
. Full of the bank.
Thank you who
had Lou Thank
God
led.
Lukumi about.
Thank
you all.
About Luke. Of the
Hank lend
a hand.
The owner
of was
my
. Head I'm
going to have.
A clue
who have
to have
.
Absolutely
thank you that's GOOD THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK all
of. Was.
The way the out.
Of the out
of that
of the
elevator
who was my thanks
to whatever who was.
About that of the. Full
of
us
. About Us.
Of the.
Blue
all
of
my.
Thank God
Thank you all.
The Oath the
oath of the athletes
who looted the US.
Led to abide.
By our loop the thing
.
For her own.
The Own Thang go
out the thrill of the
owner
that now our. Thanks to
our the oath of the
Thank
thank you at.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK YOU. THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK YOU. THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK YOU.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK.
YOU THANK. YOU THANK.
You. Thank.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK
YOU.
Thank you.
Sla
BUT THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU.
Thank you. Thank thank you all
of
us. Thank you.
Thank us
thank you thank you thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you thank you.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU.
Thank. You
Lord Lord
. You.
Who were. Brought.
To it.
The
.
Lose.
Lose lose
lose.
Lose
. So.
Yes.
Thank
us
. Thank you thank you.
Thank you thank you. Thank you thank.
All of thank you. THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK
YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU.
Thank you.
Thank you. The crew.
For us. To
elude
. Us.
Thank
you. Thousand.
Or two thousand.
Three thousand.
Thank you thank you.
Thank you thank you
Ed.
Thank ye
thank you
own
a. Thousand.
Thanks.
I have anything.
Live. Thank you.
Thank you. Anything.
I have.
Listened.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK
YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK YOU anything.
To any.
oh Oh
. Thank.
GOD THANK
YOU THANK YOU. Thank
Lula
da.
Silva who at.
Thousand
U.S.
Had at.
US
lose.
Her womb.
That.
Her the womb.
Thank you. If it was.
My. Have.
A have if it was my.
Have.
Have the boom.
Of.
The but if.
Have.
Of.
Us
have the but.
You have.
Have.
Of the.
Thousand. Nine hundred.
Luau
thousand.
Two
hundred
thousand nine
thirty three.
Hundred
.
Thousand.
Nine hundred.
Two hundred.
Yes.
Yes. The
B.S.
. Us.
To him.
To us.
To go over all of
us are
us who were
wounded
. Thank you of the
illusion
to. Thank you OK. Oh
yes.
Yes
if at the OAS.
Of.
Us
. Thousand.
And.
Two
Where
who lose.
Thatis
. Who
wrote.
Code. Yes.
Yes yes
yes.
Yes
. Yes.
. Thank.
Thank you. Thank you
thank.
Our US.
Thank you Lou Our that
Lula
da.
Looted loudly.
The clue of the.
Luella
blue.
Of the word
ladette
coalesce
lube. Loose.
The bow out of the hour LOU
OK. Back to our
lead
Le
Blanc and of the
lube oil
of. It
oh my that or the
had the bow
of the
bow
co-anchor the
balloon
of the bad US. Who were
that of the
boa
OA
the bid
for the book or that
or that of the
Lou that
it would.
LUBELL
a bow
of
the thanks of that leg
of the that
was of that was about.
Was about earlier Wow OK go
out
a Louis
Uchitelle
of
Thanks Lou.
Thank you all of the wow.
Louis
thank
God I.
Thank
goodness
.
Thank you about.
Thank you
Lou.
Lou. Of the
old
loud.
Abu Abbas
that was that
have
a hand. About
Luongo you ought.
To all out
of the who
was
a have. Lou
thank you that's it thank
you thank God and
of that.
Was. The
womb.
Thank you all
of
the
television
you all of. That Are Thank
you Lou all. Of
our of the hours of the
tell
our.
Web site. About
Luella
blue.
Who was
of their life
of my.
Thanks to both of us who
thought
. The
old
thank you thank you
Lou to our little
a blue. Blue Lou
thank you. Lou Lou Lou for
us
the bass.
The the Thass thank the
at. The
thank
the throughout.
All of. The
elevator.
Thank you as.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK YOU. Thank you thank you.
Thank you. THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK. YOU
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK.
YOU THANK. YOU THANK YOU.
Thank. Thank.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU.
Thank you thank you OK.
Thank. You.
Thank you.
Yes thank you
thank you. THANK YOU THANK YOU
THANK YOU. Thank you. Thank you
thank. Us thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank us.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU.
Thank you.
Lou.
Thank.
You.
Thank you thank you.
THANK YOU THANK YOU THANK YOU.
Thank you
you thank
.
Lunatic. Who wrote.
The who have
.
Who have.
To with. Louie.
Louie.
Have. The booth
have. A
clue. Who have the FOR
have to have.
Have.
Of the throwed
Lula Da in.